Regions and availability zones allow anyone to create worldwide infrastructure with ease.
区域和可用性区域允许任何人轻松创建全球基础结构
They also allow for redundancy within your platform.
它们还允许在您的平台内进行冗余
By properly using these components,
通过正确使用这些组件
you can create world-class systems in terms of both scale and reach.
您可以在规模和范围方面创建世界级的系统
Many organizations build an AWS without
许多组织构建的 AWS 没有
a firm understanding of region's and availability zones.
对区域和可用性区域的了解
More proficient companies may use availability zones correctly,
更熟练的公司可以正确使用可用性区域
but run only in one region.
但只在一个地区运行
By understanding and considering multi-region failover,
通过了解和考虑多区域故障转移
or running actively in multiple regions,
或者在多个地区积极运行
it'll be well on your way to creating an advanced platform on AWS.
就能在 AWS 上建立一个高级平台
[inaudible] AWS region's and availability zones,
AWS 区域和可用性区域
you can create a truly global platform.
您可以创建一个真正的全球平台
You can compete with any other company or service
您可以与任何其他公司或服务竞争
in terms of scale, distribution, and performance.
在规模 分布和性能方面
Many big-name companies are built on AWS.
许多大公司都建立在 AWS 上